# ---------------------------------
# ゲームオーバー時のヒント
# 0 : アイテム３つ
# 1 : アイテム６つ
# 2 : アイテム９つ
# 3 : サブアイテムあり
# ヒントはランダム
# 後ろの数字は確率(全部の数字を足して分母にした確率)
#


#0１２３４５６７８９０１２３４５６７８９０１
@0,1
(If you are seeing this you must die a lot...)
This message is Rare! Make sure to remember it!

@0,10
Jou just saw a secret message.
But it won't help you


@0,50
To bad, Huh?
Hehehe... I'm not giving you a hint!

@0,50
Anata ga awruidesu
~あなたが悪いです~

@0,100
Uhm... You died.
Just saying...

@0,100
Lol you´re dead!
^^

@0,100
Jay, you died
I lack of ideas!

@0,100
This is not fake difficulty
this is just hard.

@0,100
Come on!
This is easy!

@0,100
Mima Hijack
Lol

@0,100
You. are. not.
 

@0,100
couldn't see his face but              
          I could see the back of his body...

@0,100
He had blue scrubs on...


@0,100
[I never was in Braunschweig]


@0,100
...
Could you play a little bit better? Just a little?

@0,100
You're strong! I HAVE to know that 
(I programmed your charackter in the end)

@0,100
Lets beat the foe!
It's just a matter of time!

@0,70
This message has an 70 percent chance of popping up.
At the moment there are [35] messages to choose from.

@0,100
Have you encountered all 35 messages yet?
This is number thirty-six... Wait, what?
@0,100
A cobbler should stick to his last
Don't overstrain yourself^^

@0,100
A danger foreseen is a danger avoided.


@0,100
A friend in need is a friend indeed.


@0,100
A penny saved is a penny got


@0,100
A rolling stone gathers no moss.


@0,100
Actions speak louder than words.


@0,100
All mouth and no trousers, huh?
 
 
@0,100
Dirty water will quench fire.


@0,100
Saru mo ki kara ochiru.
~猿も木から落ちる~

@0,100
Just try again
~弁慶の泣き所~

@0,100
Ikihaji kaku yori, shinu ga mashi
~生き恥かくより 死ぬがまし~

@0,100
Baka wa shinanakya naoranai.
~馬鹿は死ななきゃ直らない~

@0,100
Yudan taiteki.
~油断大敵~

@0,100
Kanjō atte, zeni tarazu
~勘定合って銭足らず~

@0,100
So you died...
Well done!

@0,100
You're good!
Keep up the good work!

@0,100
Did you know ~#1~
that Touhou has an unofficial debug version?

@1,100
New Items - New Messages
Lets Speak further~
